A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Activities, Series A FA338
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subseries 2, 1941-1980; 2; 15 document box(es)
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller, Acknowledgment of Memorial Contributions, 1979 March (Box 14, Folder 173)
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller, Acknowledgment of Memorial Contributions, 1979 April (Box 14, Folder 174)
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller, Acknowledgment of Memorial Contributions, 1979 June-July (Box 14, Folder 175)
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller, Thank-You Letters for Prominent Condolences, 1979 February-April (Box 14, Folder 176)
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller, Condolence Thank-You Letters: A, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 177)
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller, Condolence Thank-You Letters: B, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 178)
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller, Condolence Thank-You Letters: C-D, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 179)
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller, Condolence Thank-You Letters: E-F, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 180)
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller, Condolence Thank-You Letters: G, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 181)
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller, Condolence Thank-You Letters: I, J, K, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 182)
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller, Condolence Thank-You Letters: L, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 183)
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller, Condolence Thank-You Letters: M, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 184)
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller, Condolence Thank-You Letters: N-O, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 185)
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller, Condolence Thank-You Letters: P-Q, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 186)
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller, Condolence Thank-You Letters: R, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 187)
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller, Condolence Thank-You Letters: S, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 188)
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller, Condolence Thank-You Letters: T-V, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 189)
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller, Condolence Thank-You Letters: W-Z, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 190)
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller, General Correspondence: A-B, 197-1980 (Box 15, Folder 191)
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller, General Correspondence: C-D, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 192)
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller, General Correspondence: E-H, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 193)
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller, General Correspondence: I-K, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 194)
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller, General Correspondence: L-O, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 195)
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller, General Correspondence: P-S, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 196)
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller, General Correspondence: T-Z, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 197)